the man chosen to transport the bomb
would be Colonel Paul tibbit who would
pilot a b29 super Fortress named anola
gay after his mother taking off at 2:45
a.m. on August 6th 1945 the anola gay
would make a 6-hour trip before arriving
in the skies above
Hiroshima that morning just before 11:15
a.m. the plan's Bombay doors would swing
open with a little boy making its way
down to the city below 600 yard from
from the ground and directly above
shima's Surgical Clinic the world's
first atomic bomb to be dropped on a
civilian population was detonated within
seconds an enormous flash of white light
burst out from the city center before a
fireball hotter than the surface of the
Sun incinerated everything in its
vicinity shock waves of unbelievable
Force followed destroying buildings and
roads for miles around with radioactive
dust and soot soon filling the air a
mushroom